{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{-\\infty}^{\\infty} \\frac{1}{\\sqrt{x^{2}+4}}dx$",
      "attempts": "attempt1",
      "answer": " diverges",
      "answer2": null,
      "prompt": "Evaluate the following definite integral",
      "extra": "Submit 'diverges' if the integral is divergent",
      "solution": "$diverges$",
      "buttonName": "b1",
      "submission": "s1"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{1}^{\\infty} \\frac{sin^2{x}+cos^2{x}}{x^{10}}dx$",
      "attempts": "attempt2",
      "answer": "\\frac{1}{9}",
      "answer2": 0.111111,
      "prompt": "Evaluate the following definite integral",
      "extra": "Submit 'diverges' if the integral is divergent",
      "solution": "$\\frac{1}{9}$",
      "buttonName": "b2",
      "submission": "s2"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int sec^4(x)tan^5(x)dx$",
      "attempts": "attempt3",
      "answer": "\\frac{{ tan}^{6}~ x}{6}+\\frac{{ tan}^{8}~ x}{8}",
      "answer2": 2380.670272,
      "prompt": "Evaluate the following indefinite integral",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically (Do not include +C)",
      "solution": "$\\frac{{ tan}^{6}~ x}{6}+\\frac{{ tan}^{8}~ x}{8}$",
      "buttonName": "b3",
      "submission": "s3"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{0}^{1} \\frac{sec^2{x}}{x\\sqrt{x}} dx$",
      "attempts": "attempt4",
      "answer": " diverges",
      "answer2": null,
      "prompt": "Use the Comparison Theorem to determine whether the integral is convergent or divergent",
      "extra": "Enter 'diverges' or 'converges' as your answer",
      "solution": "$diverges$",
      "buttonName": "b4",
      "submission": "s4"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{1}^{\\infty} (\\frac{1}{3})^{x} dx$",
      "attempts": "attempt5",
      "answer": "\\frac{1}{3\\cdot\\mathrm{ln}\\left(3\\right)}",
      "answer2": 0.303413,
      "prompt": "Evaluate the following definite integral",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically",
      "solution": "$\\frac{1}{3\\ln{3}} $",
      "buttonName": "b5",
      "submission": "s5"
    },
    {
      "question": "$a_n = \\frac{2n^{2}}{n^{2}-16}$",
      "attempts": "attempt6",
      "answer": "2",
      "answer2": 2,
      "prompt": "Find the limit of the following sequence",
      "extra": "",
      "solution": "$2$",
      "buttonName": "b6",
      "submission": "s6"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\sum_{i=1}^{70} \\frac{2^{i-2}}{3^{i-1}}$",
      "attempts": "attempt7",
      "answer": "1.5",
      "answer2": 1.5,
      "prompt": "Evaluate the following sum",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically",
      "solution": "$\\frac{3}{2}$",
      "buttonName": "b7",
      "submission": "s7"
    },
    {
      "question": "$a_{n+1} = f(a_{n})$ and $\\lim_{n\\rightarrow \\infty} a_{n} = L$",
      "attempts": "attempt8",
      "answer": "false",
      "answer2": null,
      "prompt": "A recursive relation converges at a fixed point when: ",
      "extra": "Enter 'true' or 'false'",
      "solution": "$false$",
      "buttonName": "b8",
      "submission": "s8"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "attempts": "attempt9",
      "answer": "false",
      "answer2": null,
      "prompt": "A series which is increasing, negative, and continous for the entire domain defintely diverges ",
      "extra": "Enter 'true' or 'false'",
      "solution": "$false$",
      "buttonName": "b9",
      "submission": "s9"
    },
    {
      "question": "$a_{n} = 1 + \\sqrt{\\frac{1}{1+a_{n-1}}}$",
      "attempts": "attempt10",
      "answer": "1.414214",
      "answer2": 1.414214,
      "prompt": "Assuming the limit exits, find the limit of the following recursive sequence: ",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically",
      "solution": "$\\sqrt{2}$",
      "buttonName": "b10",
      "submission": "s10"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\sum_{n=1}^{\\infty} sec ({\\frac{\\sqrt{n+2}-3}{n-7}})-1$",
      "attempts": "attempt11",
      "answer": "true",
      "answer2": null,
      "prompt": "Use the divergence test on the following series",
      "extra": "Enter 'false' if it fails the divergence test, and 'true' if it passes it",
      "solution": "$true$",
      "buttonName": "b11",
      "submission": "s11"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\sum_{n=2}^{\\infty} \\frac{1}{x^{2}-4}$",
      "attempts": "attempt12",
      "answer": "false",
      "answer2": null,
      "prompt": "If applicable, use the integral test on the following series",
      "extra": "Enter 'false' if it fails the integral test, and 'true' if it passes it",
      "solution": "$false$",
      "buttonName": "b12",
      "submission": "s12"
    },
    {
      "question": "$\\int_{0}^{2} \\frac{x^{2}-4}{\\sqrt{x}}$",
      "attempts": "attempt13",
      "answer": "-9.05096679919",
      "answer2": -9.050967,
      "prompt": "Evaluate the following definite integral",
      "extra": "Enter your answer symbolically",
      "solution": "$\\frac{8\\sqrt{2}}{5}-8\\sqrt{2}$",
      "buttonName": "b13",
      "submission": "s13"
    }
  ]
}
